edelkrone.com 2019-12-13

# Privacy Policy - edelkrone

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?  
We collect information from you when you register on our website, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. Your information is held by us and processed on computers located in the United States. However, personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in another country.

When ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, shipping and billing address(es), phone number(s) and/or credit card information. You may, however, choose to visit our site anonymously.

\----

YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us using the contact information provided below:

See what data we have about you, if any.  
Change/correct any data we have about you.  
Have us delete any data we have about you.  
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

\----

WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?  
The information we collect from you may be used in any of the following ways:

To personalize your experience  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

To improve our website  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

To improve customer service  
Such information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested or in connection with the sale of edelkrone or substantially all of its assets.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

To send periodic e-newsletter

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

\----

LUCKY ORANGE WEB ANALYTICS SERVICE  
This site uses the Lucky Orange analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience. Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity. Lucky Orange may record keystroke information that you voluntarily enter on this website. Lucky Orange does not track this activity on any site that does not use the Lucky Orange system. You can choose to disable the Lucky Orange Service here. Please note, however, that doing so will disable other features of the Lucky Orange system that this site employs such as 1-to-1 support chat.

\----

HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then stored in the “Vault” on Braintree (a PayPal company) servers. The Vault securely stores customer information, including payment methods. When a payment method is stored in the Vault, the information is encrypted by the Braintree gateway.

While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do this at your own risk.

\----

DO WE USE COOKIES?  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

\----

DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?  
Other than as expressly provided for herein, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also include your information in connection with the sale of edelkrone or substantially all of its assets, and we may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, cooperate with government officials in any investigation relating to any content (including personal or private electronic communications transmitted to edelkrone) or purported unlawful activities of any user, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

\----

CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), and we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

\----

ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY ONLY  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

\----

THIRD PARTY SERVICES  
We never post anything to your accounts with Facebook, Twitter, or any other third party sites without your permission.

\----

TERMS AND CONDITIONS  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our products and website.

\----

YOUR CONSENT  
By using our site, you consent to our website privacy policy.

\----

UPDATES  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page. If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately using the contact information provided below.

\----

CONTACTING US  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us at contact.edelkrone.com or using the information below.

edelkrone USA Inc.  
7307 Sandscove Court Ste 7  
Winter Park, FL 32792
